(HR Woman:)Cancel my next appointment.
This is gonna take a while.
(HR Woman:)Dr. Cooper, you said things
to your employee...
(HR Woman:)...that you just cannot say
in the workplace.
(Sheldon:)Like what?
(HR Woman:)Well, according to Ms. Jensen you said...
(HR Woman:)...that she was a
"slave to her biological urges"...
...and called her an "egg salad sandwich."
(HR Woman:)I don't even know what that means...
(HR Woman:)...but I'm gonna go ahead
and tell you you can't say it.
Oh, I see the confusion here.
(Sheldon:)Alex thought I was singling her out. No.
(Sheldon:)I meant that all women
are slaves to their biological urges.
(Sheldon:)Even you.
(Sheldon:)You're a slave.
(HR Woman:)I'm a what?